xbox-scene.com 2002-06-07

# Xbox Scene

**Privacy Policy**  
By Xantium  
November 10, 2001 

**Privacy Policy**  
Xbox-Scene is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**Basic Confidentiality Policy**  
It is policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you may provide us, such as through our forum, chat or by email used only for the purposes for which you provide the information. For example, if you choose to give your name and/or any other personal information it is completely by your own will. 

Xbox-Scene will not solicit or provide any private information to outside vendors or organizations. Information you choose to submit on our site is for public view and at your discretion. Therefore any information you submit publicly on Xbox-Scene.com by way of forums or chats can be viewed by outside sources. Any emails submitted to any member of Xbox-Scene will remain privately held and no such information will be made public unless user permission is granted. 

**No Computer Tracking of Identifiable Information**  
Our server is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors. It does recognize the home server of visitors, but not e-mail addresses. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our sites. This information is used only for internal purposes by Xbox-Scene technical support staff. 

In addition, our website tracks information about the visits to our website. For example, we compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our sites, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our web sites, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used internally to better provide services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. 

**Xbox-Scene is not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of any affiliates or 3rd party organizations displayed within our website.**  

If you have questions or suggestions send an email to [admin@Xbox-Scene.com](mailto:admin@Xbox-Scene.com).
